ucbtheatre.com 2019-09-02

# UCBComedy

The following websites and mobile application (collectively, the " **Websites** "), are owned and operated by the Upright Citizens Brigade, LLC (" **UCB** ," " **us** " or " **our** "): 

  * uprightcitizens.org
  * UCBcomedy.com
  * UCBtheatre.com
  * UCBstore.com
  * delclosemarathon.com
  * UCB marathon mobile application
  * innersanctumcafe.com
  * UCBcomedy.edu
  * UCBinnersanctum.com
  * UCBtheater.com
  * UCBtheatre.com
  * UCBt.net
  * UCBtourco.com
  * UCBtrainingcenter.com
  * UCBindustries.com
  * UCBworkplace.com
  * dontthinkproductions.com

The Websites are a forum for UCB students, performers, consumers and others to access and share information about UCB. This Privacy Notice explains how we collect information through the Websites, and use and disclose that information.  
  
The terms governing the use of our Websites are set forth at [UCBcomedy.com/terms] (our " **Terms of Use** "). This Privacy Notice is incorporated within and made a part of the Terms of Use.

  1. **Information We Collect.  
**  
(a) **Personally Identifiable Information.**  We collect the personally identifiable information that you provide us. This may occur in a variety of ways, such as when you register an account on a Website (" **Account** "), fill out a form, send us an inquiry or feedback, or in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available via our Websites. The information may include, for example, your name, e-mail address, mailing address and/or phone number. The decision to provide such information is up to you; you may visit our Websites without providing any personally identifiable information. If you choose not to provide personally identifiable information, you may not be able to use certain features, such as registering an Account.  
  
(b) **Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**  We may collect non-personally identifiable information about users whenever they interact with our Websites. Non-personally identifiable information may include certain technical information that identifies the computer or device, software and Internet Service Provider (ISP) requesting access to the Websites, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address (a unique number that is automatically assigned to a computer when surfing the web); MAC address (a unique number that is assigned to a network card by the manufacturer); date/time stamps for the visit; domain name; browser type and version; and/or operating system.  
  
(c) **Location Information.** If a Website is accessed using a browser, we may collect location information provided by the ISP, such as general geographic location. If a Website is accessed using a mobile device, we may also collect location information provided by the location services features of the mobile device, such as more specific location positioning or latitude/longitude information.  
  
(d) **Cookies.**  We may use "cookies" or other technologies to enhance a user's experience. Through the user's web browser, a cookie is placed on the hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about the user. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do, some parts of the Websites may not function properly.  

  2.  **How We Use Information.**

We may use the information we collect for the following purposes:  
  
(a) **To Improve Customer Service.**  Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
  
(b) **For Casting.**  We may use information for purposes of casting, internally within UCB organizations, as well for casting with other organizations.  
  
(c) **To Personalize the User Experience.**  We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided via our Websites.  
  
(d) **To Improve Our Websites.**  We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
  
(e) **To Send Periodic E-mails.**  We may use your e-mail address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests, and to send informational and/or promotional e-mail to you on behalf of UCB and third parties.  

  3.  **How We Disclose Information.  
**  
(a) Except as indicated in this Privacy Notice, we do not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information to others. We may share non-personally identifiable information, de-identified information or generic aggregated information (such as demographic information not linked to any personally identifiable information) regarding our Websites' visitors, with third parties, such as our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers, for the purposes outlined in Section 2 above.  
  
(b) We may share your information, which may include your personally identifiable information:  
  
(i) To process an order or to respond to your request, e.g., we will provide your name and address to a delivery company to deliver a product you requested.  
  
(ii) With third parties for casting opportunities.(iii) To our service providers who perform services on our behalf, but they are authorized to use the information only to provide a service for us, e.g., a vendor we engage to send e-mail to you.  
  
(iv) In accordance with legal process (e.g., to respond to a subpoena), or when otherwise required by law.  
  
(v) To protect our interests, such as our property or assets, or the interests of a third party; for the purposes of collecting a debt or to protect ourselves from fraud; and to investigate an anticipated or actual breach of an agreement or a contravention of law.  
  
(vi) When the information is available from a public source (e.g., a telephone directory or the Internet).  
  
(vii) With our professional advisors, such as our attorney, when we require legal or other advice.  
  
(viii) With the new owner or investor, if one of our businesses is sold or divested, or we are acquired or merged with another organization.  

  4.  **How We Protect Information.**  We utilize data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures designed to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of the information stored by our Websites. Private data exchanged between our Websites and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.  

  5.  **Third Party Ads and Websites.**  Users may find advertising or other content on our Websites that are sponsored by or link to the websites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear in these advertisements and websites and are not responsible for the practices employed by the third parties promoting them. They may have their own privacy and customer service practices. Clicking the advertisements or browsing and interacting on any other website, including a website that links to our Websites, is subject to the third party's terms and policies.  

  6.  **Advertising.**  
Ads appearing on our Websites may be delivered by advertising partners, who may set cookies via those ads. Those cookies may allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online ad, and to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information may be used by ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted ads they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Notice does not cover such practices by third party advertisers.
  7.  **Do Not Track.**  Do not track is a voluntary program among Internet advertisers that is intended to give browser users the ability to opt-out of behavioral advertising. There are a few ways in which a computer may transmit a "do not track" signal to certain websites, and currently no standard has been established. We do not respond to do not track signals, and the settings in a browser will have no effect on the information collected via the Websites.  

  8.  **Children.**  The Websites are not directed to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information to third parties. If we become aware that personal information from someone under the age of 13 was received, we will take steps to delete such information from our records. If you believe that we have personal information from someone under 13, please contact support at: support@UCBcomedy.com.  

  9.  **Outside the United States.**  The Websites are intended for U.S. users within the U.S. The Websites are not intended for use outside the U.S. If you are a non-U.S. user of the Websites, your information may be collected and processed in the country in which you reside and/or in other countries, including the U.S., where laws regarding the collection and processing of personal information may differ from the laws in your country.  

  10.  **Changes to this Privacy Policy.**  We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Notice at any time. When we do, we will revise the date at the bottom of this webpage. We encourage users to frequently check this webpage. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Notice periodically to be aware of any revisions. Your use of the Websites is subject to the most current version of this Privacy Notice.  

  11.  **Contact Us.**  If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, the practices of our Websites, or your dealings with UCB, please contact us at:  
  
Upright Citizens Brigade  
266 West 37th Street, Floor 12  
New York, NY 10018  
212-366-9176  
bugs@UCBcomedy.com

This document was last updated on November 17, 2017.

© 2017 Upright Citizens Brigade, LLC
